### Career Summary

Engineer with more than 3 years of experience in software development, with knowledge of front end in technologies such as angular 7, HTML, CSS, boostrap and JavaScript, also with backend knowledge in technologies such as Java EE, java 8, C #, development of applications in the Spring Boot framework. Management of Oracle and MySQL databases, plus knowledge of integration tools such as OSB and IBM App Connect. Also experience in cloud technologies such as AWS and GCP.

## **Summary of Qualifications**

Skills:

- Java8+
- Spring
- C#
- Docker
- MySQL
- PL/SQL SQLServer
- Dynamo
- AWS
- GCP OSB
- SQS

- WebLogic
- Unit
- Testing Kubernetes
- Kafka

Ene. 2022 – current

Feb. 2021 – Dic.2021

## Languages

Spanish (native speaker)

English (advanced)

### Career History

### EPAM Systems, Bogotá, Colombia

Sr Software developer

- Working as a Senior software developer for an insurance company in the USA
- REST services development in Spring Boot.
- Deploy applications in AWS.
- Upgrade the code of different applications from java 7 to java 17
- Deploy the services with docker and Kubernetes in AWS
- Participating in architecture design with the team
- Github and Gitlab
- JSP

## Globant, Bogotá, Colombia

Java Ssr developer

- REST services development in Spring Boot.
- Deploy applications in AWS.
- CI/CD with Jenkins

- Kubernetes
- Github and Gitlab
- Production support
- Unit and functional testing with mockito
- Agile and SCRUM methodologies

# Masivian, Bogotá, Colombia

Sept. 2020 – Feb.2021

Software engineer

• Worked on Disney Centralised Accounting Platform.

- Lambdas development for different process in different lenguages.
- Step functions
- Dockerizing applications
- Web development with Angular 7 and Node JS

- Application development in c#
- Deploy applications and infrastructure in AWS
- Participation in architecture design in AWS
- Azure Devops
- Agile and SCRUM methodologies

# IBM, Bogotá, Colombia

Java application developer

- Service development in OSB and IBM App Connect
- Google cloud certification: associate cloud engineer
- Dockerizing applications
- Analysis and design of client requirements

Jun. 2019 - Sept.2020

- Construction and consumption of REST/SOAP services with Spring
- Git management
- Web development with Angular
- Agile and SCRUM methodologies
- Application development with Java 8+

Intern Jan. 2019 – Jun. 2019

- Application development with Java, Angular
- Management of Oracle and MySQL databases
- Using CD tools for CI/CD like Jenkins and Travis

## Education

**National university of Colombia**, Bogota, Colombia BS, Mechatronic Engineering

Jan. 2012 - Nov. 2019